<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<rdf:RDF
 xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
 xmlns="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/"
 xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
 xmlns:taxo="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/taxonomy/"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:syn="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
 xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/"
>

<channel rdf:about="">
<title>SCAMIT News and Events</title>
<link></link>
<description>Southern California Association of Marine Invertebrate Taxonomists</description>
<items>
 <rdf:Seq>
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#smith" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#mesls" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#ecoanalysts" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://www.scamit.org/index.html#Nov15" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://www.scamit.org/index.html#Dec10" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://www.scamit.org/index.html#Dec11" />
 </rdf:Seq>
</items>
</channel>
<item rdf:about="http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#smith">
<title>&#x3C;a name=&#x22;smith&#x22;&#x3E;Smithsonian National Museum of Natural History&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
&#x3C;b&#x3E;Invertebrate Zoologist&#x3C;/b&#x3E;
</title>
<link>http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#smith</link>
<description>&#x3C;i&#x3E;1 November 2010&#x3C;br /&#x3E; If you might be interested in joining the Smithsonian NMNH community as a research zoologist, please check out the advertisement linked below.&#x3C;br /&#x3E; Job Title: Research Zoologist&#x3C;br /&#x3E; Agency: Smithsonian Institution&#x3C;br /&#x3E; Sub Agency: Smithsonian&#x3C;br /&#x3E; Job Announcement Number: 11A-RB-296421-DEU-NMNH&#x3C;br /&#x3E; SALARY RANGE: $74,872.00 - $79,864.00 /year&#x3C;br /&#x3E; OPEN PERIOD: Friday, October 29, 2010 to Friday, December 10, 2010&#x3C;br /&#x3E; SERIES &#x26;amp; GRADE: GS-0410-12/12&#x3C;br /&#x3E; POSITION INFORMATION: Full-Time Term Appointment NTE 4 years.&#x3C;br /&#x3E; PROMOTION POTENTIAL: 12&#x3C;br /&#x3E; DUTY LOCATIONS: 1 vacancy - Washington DC Metro Area, DC&#x3C;br /&#x3E; WHO MAY BE CONSIDERED: This position is open to all U.S. Citizens or U.S. Nationals.&#x3C;br /&#x3E; JOB SUMMARY: This position is located in the Department of Invertebrate Zoology, National Museum of Natural History, Smithsonian Institution. The employee will perform scholarly scientific research and professional curation in part of the National Collections relating to invertebrate evolution and biodiversity.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;&#x3C;a href=&#x22;http://jobview.usajobs.gov/GetJob.aspx?JobID=91767617&#x26;amp;JobTitle=Research+Zoologist&#x26;amp;brd=3876&#x26;amp;vw=b&#x26;amp;FedEmp=Y&#x26;amp;FedPub=Y&#x26;amp;x=83&#x26;amp;y=18&#x26;amp;jbf574=SM03&#x26;amp;pg=2&#x26;amp;re=3&#x26;amp;AVSDM=2010-10-29+00%3a03%3a00&#x22;&#x3E;Link to full job description&#x3C;/a&#x3E;.&#x3C;br /&#x3E; Dr. Allen G. Collins&#x3C;br /&#x3E; COLLINSA@si.edu&#x3C;br /&#x3E; phone: (202) 633-0645, fax: (202) 633-8848&#x3C;br /&#x3E; Zoologist, National Systematics Laboratory of NOAA Fisheries Service&#x3C;br /&#x3E; Curator, Smithsonian National Museum of Natural History&#x3C;br /&#x3E; MRC-153, P.O. Box 37012, Washington, DC 20013-7012 USA&#x3C;/i&#x3E;
</description>
</item>
<item rdf:about="http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#mesls">
<title>&#x3C;a name=&#x22;mesls&#x22;&#x3E;Marine Ecological Surveys&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
&#x3C;b&#x3E;Senior Marine Macrobenthic Taxonomist&#x3C;/b&#x3E;
</title>
<link>http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#mesls</link>
<description>&#x3C;i&#x3E;1 September 2010&#x3C;br /&#x3E;&#x3C;a href=&#x22;http://www.seasurvey.co.uk/vacancies&#x22;&#x3E;Senior Marine Macrobenthic Taxonomist&#x3C;/a&#x3E;&#x3C;br /&#x3E; The MESL laboratory specialises in analysis of benthic and epibenthic samples from a wide variety of environments ranging from estuarine to offshore. Primarily our work consists of monitoring for the aggregate industry and, more recently, the renewable energy sector. Our staff comprise of an experienced team of marine biologists who are self-motivated and work to tight deadlines.&#x3C;br /&#x3E; We are looking for a senior marine macrobenthic taxonomist whose primary role will be to undertake analysis of benthic samples and identification of all taxonomic groups, together with training of junior staff in benthic taxonomy. You will be educated to at least degree level in marine biology or a related discipline and also have at least two years experience in marine invertebrate analysis and taxonomic identification. While you will be mostly lab-based, you will also be required to participate in fieldwork.&#x3C;br /&#x3E; MESL participates in the NMBAQC scheme, and in conjunction with this, we run our own internal training scheme to develop the taxonomic skills of our laboratory staff. We also encourage continued professional development for all our staff.&#x3C;br /&#x3E; Please email your CV to &#x3C;a href=&#x22;mailto:lab@seasurvey.co.uk&#x22;&#x3E;lab@seasurvey.co.uk&#x3C;/a&#x3E;&#x3C;br /&#x3E; Sara Marzialetti&#x3C;br /&#x3E; Senior Marine Ecologist&#x3C;br /&#x3E; Marine Ecological Surveys Limited&#x3C;br /&#x3E; 3 Palace Yard Mews&#x3C;br /&#x3E; Bath&#x3C;br /&#x3E; BA1 2NH&#x3C;br /&#x3E; England&#x3C;br /&#x3E; Tel: 01225 442211&#x3C;br /&#x3E; Fax: 01225 444411&#x3C;/i&#x3E;
</description>
</item>
<item rdf:about="http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#ecoanalysts">
<title>&#x3C;a name=&#x22;ecoanalysts&#x22;&#x3E;EcoAnalysts&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
&#x3C;b&#x3E;Multiple marine taxonomists&#x3C;/b&#x3E;
</title>
<link>http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#ecoanalysts</link>
<description>&#x3C;i&#x3E;22 June 2010&#x3C;/i&#x3E;
&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 EcoAnalysts, Inc. has been awarded a contract by the US EPA to collect and analyze samples from the nation&#x27;s coasts in an effort to monitor and evaluate the ecological and environmental conditions in US waters. Please visit our Employment Opportunities page on our website at &#x3C;a href=&#x22;http://www.ecoanalysts.com&#x22;&#x3E;www.ecoanalysts.com&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
&#x3C;i&#x3E;Eric Torok&#x3C;/i&#x3E;
&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 Human Resources Coordinator&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 1420 S. Blaine St., Suite 14&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 Moscow, ID 83843&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 etorok@ecoanalysts.com</description>
</item>
<item rdf:about="http://www.scamit.org/index.html#Nov15">
<title>&#x3C;a name=&#x22;Nov15&#x22;&#x3E;&#x3C;b&#x3E;Monday 15 November 2010 9:30 AM&#x3C;/b&#x3E;&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
&#x3C;i&#x3E;Mollusk literature review and Taxonomic Database testbed demo&#x3C;/i&#x3E;
 at OCSD meeting room.</title>
<link>http://www.scamit.org/index.html#Nov15</link>
<description>Mollusk literature review, followed by a demo of the testing version of the new Taxonomic Database. Non-mollusk taxonomists who are likely to be extensive users of the Taxonomic Database can attend the demo to see its features and provide feedback for further development.</description>
</item>
<item rdf:about="http://www.scamit.org/index.html#Dec10">
<title>&#x3C;a name=&#x22;Dec10&#x22;&#x3E;&#x3C;b&#x3E;Friday 10 November 2010 9:30&#x26;ndash;3:30&#x3C;/b&#x3E;&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
&#x3C;i&#x3E;Arthropoda: Crustacea literature review&#x3C;/i&#x3E;
 at LACSD.</title>
<link>http://www.scamit.org/index.html#Dec10</link>
<description>Don Cadien will lead a review of new Arthropoda: Crustacea literature with emphasis on papers reporting newly described/reported species to S. Cal. or revisionary papers effecting name usage or taxonomic hierarchy of our local fauna. Dr. Mary Wicksten will be attend the meeting to contribute and discuss her recent work on Eastern Pacific decapods. I hope all our local crustacean taxonomists will plan on attending this meeting. Don will be sending out more information prior to the meeting.</description>
</item>
<item rdf:about="http://www.scamit.org/index.html#Dec11">
<title>&#x3C;a name=&#x22;Dec11&#x22;&#x3E;&#x3C;b&#x3E;Saturday 11 December 2010 5:30&#x26;ndash;9:00&#x26;nbsp;PM&#x3C;/b&#x3E;&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
&#x3C;i&#x3E;SCAMIT Christmas Party&#x3C;/i&#x3E;
 at Cabrillo Marine Aquarium.</title>
<link>http://www.scamit.org/index.html#Dec11</link>
<description>All SCAMIT members and their families are invited to attend. In addition, the officers decided it would be neighborly to invite members and their families of our two sister groups to join us. Invitations will be extended to the members of the Southwestern Association of Freshwater Invertebrate Taxonomists (SAFIT) and the Southern California Association of Ichthyological Taxonomists and Ecologists (SCAITE). It should make for a lively event. More details later.</description>
</item>
</rdf:RDF>