<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<rdf:RDF
 xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
 xmlns="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/"
 xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
 xmlns:taxo="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/taxonomy/"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:syn="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
 xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/"
>

<channel rdf:about="">
<title>SCAMIT News and Events</title>
<link></link>
<description>Southern California Association of Marine Invertebrate Taxonomists</description>
<items>
 <rdf:Seq>
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#ecoanalysts" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#ost" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://www.scamit.org/index.html#Aug23&#x27;" />
 </rdf:Seq>
</items>
</channel>
<item rdf:about="http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#ecoanalysts">
<title>&#x3C;a name=&#x22;ecoanalysts&#x22;&#x3E;EcoAnalysts&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
&#x3C;b&#x3E;Multiple marine taxonomists&#x3C;/b&#x3E;
</title>
<link>http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#ecoanalysts</link>
<description>&#x3C;i&#x3E;22 June 2010&#x3C;/i&#x3E;
&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 EcoAnalysts, Inc. has been awarded a contract by the US EPA to collect and analyze samples from the nation&#x27;s coasts in an effort to monitor and evaluate the ecological and environmental conditions in US waters. Please visit our Employment Opportunities page on our website at &#x3C;a href=&#x22;http://www.ecoanalysts.com&#x22;&#x3E;www.ecoanalysts.com&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
&#x3C;i&#x3E;Eric Torok&#x3C;/i&#x3E;
&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 Human Resources Coordinator&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 1420 S. Blaine St., Suite 14&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 Moscow, ID 83843&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 etorok@ecoanalysts.com</description>
</item>
<item rdf:about="http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#ost">
<title>&#x3C;a name=&#x22;ost&#x22;&#x3E;California Ocean Science Trust (OST)&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
&#x3C;b&#x3E;Assistant Scientist, Marine Protected Areas Monitoring Enterprise&#x3C;br /&#x3E; Knowledge Manager, Marine Protected Areas Monitoring Enterprise&#x3C;/b&#x3E;
</title>
<link>http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#ost</link>
<description>&#x3C;i&#x3E;4 Nov 2009&#x3C;/i&#x3E;
&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 The California Ocean Science Trust (OST) is a nonprofit 501(c)(3) public benefit corporation established pursuant to the California Ocean Resources Stewardship Act of 2000 to encourage coordinated, multi-agency, multi-institution approaches to translating ocean science to management and policy applications. The Marine Protected Areas Monitoring Enterprise was launched in 2007 under the auspices of the OST to lead development of efficient, cost-effective monitoring of the statewide marine protected areas (MPA) network being established under the Marine Life Protection Act. The MPA Monitoring Enterprise, which is supported by the Ocean Protection Council and works in partnership with the Department of Fish and Game, has two new job openings, for an Assistant Scientist and a Knowledge Manager. Both positions will be based in Oakland, California, in the offices of the OST. Start date for both positions is as soon as possible, preferably by March 1, 2010. Review of applications will begin January 4, 2010.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
Full position descriptions, which include application information, can be found at: &#x3C;a href=&#x22;http://www.calost.org/monitoring_ent.html&#x22;&#x3E;http://www.calost.org/monitoring_ent.html&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
.</description>
</item>
<item rdf:about="http://www.scamit.org/index.html#Aug23&#x27;">
<title>&#x3C;a name=&#x22;Aug23&#x26;#39;&#x22;&#x3E;&#x3C;b&#x3E;Monday 23 August 2010 9:30 AM&#x3C;/b&#x3E;&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
&#x3C;i&#x3E;Bight&#x26;nbsp;&#x26;rsquo;08 Infaunal QA resolution&#x3C;/i&#x3E;
 meeting at LACSD labs. </title>
<link>http://www.scamit.org/index.html#Aug23&#x27;</link>
<description>Specific labs will be directly involved, but all interested parties are invited to attend to see the resolution process and those taxa reviewed will likely be those that are more problematic. Cheryl Brantley will be sending out more specific information towards the end of July, and will discuss the Bight QA resolution schedules for September and October as well.</description>
</item>
</rdf:RDF>