<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<rdf:RDF
 xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
 xmlns="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/"
 xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
 xmlns:taxo="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/taxonomy/"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:syn="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
 xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/"
>

<channel rdf:about="">
<title>SCAMIT News and Events</title>
<link></link>
<description>Southern California Association of Marine Invertebrate Taxonomists</description>
<items>
 <rdf:Seq>
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#sc" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#orangecounty" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#ecoanalysts" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://www.scamit.org/index.html#Aug15b" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://www.scamit.org/index.html#Sep2011" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://www.scamit.org/index.html#c15e585619e8ddda069b44dee067fb63" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://www.scamit.org/index.html#ad69d2a17e9a4bd9b13d43e71eac672c" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://www.scamit.org/index.html#0b47b3996b6cce03b5d6b615322c3be6" />
 </rdf:Seq>
</items>
</channel>
<item rdf:about="http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#sc">
<title>&#x3C;a name=&#x22;sc&#x22;&#x3E;Associate Marine Scientist (Benthic Ecology/Environmental Research)&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
&#x3C;b&#x3E;South Carolina Department of Natural Resources&#x3C;/b&#x3E;
</title>
<link>http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#sc</link>
<description>&#x3C;i&#x3E;June 5, 2011 &#x26;ndash; July 5, 2011&#x3C;/i&#x3E;
&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 Job status: Full-time/permanent Work schedule: 8:30am &#x2013; 5:00pm Monday through Friday, but fieldwork may require occasional 10 or more work hrs. per day and work on weekends.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 Location: Charleston, SC.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 Hiring range: $50,000 &#x2013; $55,000 / yr. dependent on work experience&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
&#x3C;b&#x3E;Job Description:&#x3C;/b&#x3E;
 Supervises and conducts research on marine environmental concerns in South Carolina as section manager of the Environmental Research section within the SCDNR&#x27;s Marine Resources Research Instiatute, with technical expertise in benthic ecology. Current studies involve beach nourishment and beach modifications, effects of land use on marine and estuarine biota and habitats, and comprehensive monitoring of the State&#x27;s coastal habitats to assess condition.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
&#x3C;b&#x3E;Minimum education and experience:&#x3C;/b&#x3E;
 Ph.D. in marine science, zoology or biology; specialization benthic ecology/environmental research and at least 3 years of post-graduate owrking iexperience relevant to ecology/environmental science. Statitistical expertise in analyzing large data sets, supervisory experience, demonstrated technical writhing experience.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
&#x3C;b&#x3E;Other preferred knowledge, skills, and abilities:&#x3C;/b&#x3E;
Ability to conduct and lead research as demonstrated by preparation of successful research proposals, completion of research and reports, and peer reviewed publications. Familiarity with benthic ecology and environmental literature, experience and ability in inshore and offshore benthic sampling procedures. ability to swim and lift 50 lb. and participate in field work on daily basis or longer time periods, occasional out- of-town overnight stays, occasional weekend work or working outside of normal hours, ability to work in laboratory in presence of preservatives. Individual must be self motivated, have excellent interpersonnal and time management skills, and attention to detail.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
&#x3C;b&#x3E;To apply:&#x3C;/b&#x3E;
Apply online at &#x3C;a href=&#x22;http://www.state.sc.us/jobs/application&#x22;&#x3E;http://www.state.sc.us/jobs/application&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
. Agency: Department of Natural Resources&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 PLEASE NOTE: Applicants should submit a letter of interest, cv, and statement of qualifications as part of the application. Applicants must be able to legally work in the United States.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 For further information e-mail: &#x3C;a href=&#x22;mailto:vandolahr@dnr.sc.us&#x22;&#x3E;vandolahr@dnr.sc.us&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 Submit a state application to the following address no later than the closing date:&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 OPEN DATE: June 5, 2011&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 CLOSING DATE: July 5, 2011&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 Office of Human Resources&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 Department of Natural Resources&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 P.O. Box 167, 1000 Assembly Street&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 Columbia, South Carolina 29202-0167&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 (803) 734-4400&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 EMAIL: JOBS@DNR.SC.GOV&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 College transcripts must be available upon request. South Carolina Department of Natural Resources is an EEO/AA Employer.</description>
</item>
<item rdf:about="http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#orangecounty">
<title>&#x3C;a name=&#x22;orangecounty&#x22;&#x3E;Orange County Environmental Specialist&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
&#x3C;b&#x3E;Orange County Sanitation District&#x3C;/b&#x3E;
&#x3C;b&#x3E;Principal Environmental Specialist&#x3C;/b&#x3E;
</title>
<link>http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#orangecounty</link>
<description>&#x3C;i&#x3E;7 June 2011&#x3C;/i&#x3E;
&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 The Orange County Sanitation District (OCSD) seeks a Principal Environmental Specialist for its Infaunal Taxonomy Program. Located in southern California, OCSD is a public agency that is dedicated to maintaining world-class leadership in wastewater and water resource management, operating and maintaining the third largest wastewater treatment facilities east of the Mississippi River.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 Under general direction the Principal Environmental Specialist serves as a project leader with a wide variety of technical and administrative responsibilities within the District&#x27;s Environmental and Ocean Monitoring Laboratory. This position will have primary responsibility for management of the Infaunal Taxonomy Program. The successful candidate will possess the equivalent of a Bachelor&#x27;s degree from an accredited college or university with major course work in biological, physical, or environmental science, including coursework and lab work in invertebrate zoology. A minimum of five years of increasingly responsible experience in an environmental laboratory or field collections environment, with three years at a level comparable to a Senior Environmental Specialist with the District is required. Other requirements include: a minimum of two years of recent experience identifying marine invertebrates and familiarity with the taxonomy of at least two taxa groups (e.g. polychaetes, crustaceans, mollusks, echinoderms, or members of the &#x201C;minor phyla&#x201D;); knowledge of wastewater treatment and associated processes, invertebrate zoology and the principles of taxonomy; and experience with compound and dissection microscopes and micro-dissection techniques.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 To learn more and apply, please visit &#x3C;a href=&#x22;http://www.ocsd.com/jobs&#x22;&#x3E;http://www.ocsd.com/jobs&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
. First application review will occur on 6/23/11.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 Contact information:&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 Human Resources Department&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 jobs@ocsd.com&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 Jobs Help Line: 714-593-7140</description>
</item>
<item rdf:about="http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#ecoanalysts">
<title>&#x3C;a name=&#x22;ecoanalysts&#x22;&#x3E;EcoAnalysts&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
&#x3C;b&#x3E;Multiple marine taxonomists&#x3C;/b&#x3E;
</title>
<link>http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#ecoanalysts</link>
<description>&#x3C;i&#x3E;22 June 2010&#x3C;/i&#x3E;
&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 EcoAnalysts, Inc. has been awarded a contract by the US EPA to collect and analyze samples from the nation&#x27;s coasts in an effort to monitor and evaluate the ecological and environmental conditions in US waters. Please visit our Employment Opportunities page on our website at &#x3C;a href=&#x22;http://www.ecoanalysts.com&#x22;&#x3E;www.ecoanalysts.com&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
&#x3C;i&#x3E;Eric Torok&#x3C;/i&#x3E;
&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 Human Resources Coordinator&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 1420 S. Blaine St., Suite 14&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 Moscow, ID 83843&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 etorok@ecoanalysts.com</description>
</item>
<item rdf:about="http://www.scamit.org/index.html#Aug15b">
<title>&#x3C;b&#x3E;July 2011&#x3C;/b&#x3E;
&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 Don Cadien has prepared a new version of the &#x3C;a href=&#x22;taxontools/toolbox/Phylum Arthropoda/Order Amphipoda/Amphipod Summaries_Don Cadien/Lysianassoidea of the NEPmod - 2011.pdf&#x22;&#x3E;Lysianassoidea review&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
 (Amphipoda), available in &#x3C;a href=&#x22;taxontools/index.html&#x22;&#x3E;Taxonomic Tools&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
. It includes some recent taxonomic changes as well as a revised key to the genera in the superfamily in the NEP.&#x3C;b&#x3E;July 2011&#x3C;/b&#x3E;
&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
&#x3C;i&#x3E;No meeting scheduled due to member involvement in the extensive field sampling efforts of Southern California POTW labs.&#x3C;/i&#x3E;
&#x3C;a name=&#x22;Aug15b&#x22;&#x3E;&#x3C;b&#x3E;Monday &#x3C;span class=&#x22;cancel&#x22;&#x3E;15 August&#x3C;/span&#x3E; 8 August 2011 9:30&#x26;ndash;3:30&#x3C;/b&#x3E; &#x3C;span class=&#x22;notedate&#x22;&#x3E;(Note date change)&#x3C;/span&#x3E; &#x3C;/a&#x3E;
&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
&#x3C;i&#x3E;Morphbank image submittal workshop&#x3C;/i&#x3E;
 at SCCWRP in the large conference room.</title>
<link>http://www.scamit.org/index.html#Aug15b</link>
<description>Deb Paul, Morphbank FSU, will visit us to lead another workshop on Morphbank image submittal. We will receive hands on experience using two modes of image submittal. We will submit images using the online Morphbank website system in the morning, then use the newer spreadsheet submittal system in the afternoon. Those attending should bring 10 - 20 benthic invertebrate images with supporting collection information. This is planned as a productive day of uploading new images to Morphbank. Those who cannot attend will be able to follow the meeting online via SCCWRP&#x27;s web conferencing. Details for web access to follow.</description>
</item>
<item rdf:about="http://www.scamit.org/index.html#Sep2011">
<title>&#x3C;a name=&#x22;Sep2011&#x22;&#x3E;&#x3C;b&#x3E;Monday 12 September 2011 9:30&#x26;ndash;3:30&#x3C;/b&#x3E;&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
&#x3C;i&#x3E;Enteropneusta&#x3C;/i&#x3E;
 at Lilly Pad Environmental, Escondido, CA (directions to follow).</title>
<link>http://www.scamit.org/index.html#Sep2011</link>
<description>Megan will lead a workshop on Enteropneusta. Those who plan to attend are asked to use their July field sampling events to pull specimens for special handling and preservation during collection. That way materials in excellent condition will be available for the meeting. We hope to improve the level of identification for this group at this meeting.</description>
</item>
<item rdf:about="http://www.scamit.org/index.html#c15e585619e8ddda069b44dee067fb63">
<title>&#x3C;a name=&#x22;&#x22;&#x3E;&#x3C;b&#x3E;Monday 17 October 2011 9:30&#x26;ndash;3:30&#x3C;/b&#x3E;&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
&#x3C;i&#x3E;Enopla Bight&#x26;nbsp;&#x26;rsquo;08 specialty taxonomy presentation&#x3C;/i&#x3E;
 at OCSD.</title>
<link>http://www.scamit.org/index.html#c15e585619e8ddda069b44dee067fb63</link>
<description>Tony Phillips will present his findings from the Bight&#xA0;&#x2019;08 samples. He will review the characters used to identify the species and have specimens for examination. Bring any strange enoplans from your regular samples you need help with to this meeting.</description>
</item>
<item rdf:about="http://www.scamit.org/index.html#ad69d2a17e9a4bd9b13d43e71eac672c">
<title>&#x3C;a name=&#x22;&#x22;&#x3E;&#x3C;b&#x3E;Monday 14 November 2011 9:30&#x26;ndash;3:30&#x3C;/b&#x3E;&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
&#x3C;i&#x3E;Syllidae Bight&#x26;nbsp;&#x26;rsquo;08 specialty taxonomy presentation&#x3C;/i&#x3E;
 at City of San Diego Environmental Monitoring Lab.</title>
<link>http://www.scamit.org/index.html#ad69d2a17e9a4bd9b13d43e71eac672c</link>
<description>Ron Velarde will present the results of his Bight&#xA0;&#x2019;08 work on this difficult polychaete family. There will be updates to the current name usage presented and important character states will be reviewed. There is sure to be new information on this family presented at this meeting. </description>
</item>
<item rdf:about="http://www.scamit.org/index.html#0b47b3996b6cce03b5d6b615322c3be6">
<title>&#x3C;a name=&#x22;&#x22;&#x3E;&#x3C;b&#x3E;Monday 12 December 2011 9:30&#x26;ndash;3:30&#x3C;/b&#x3E;&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
&#x3C;i&#x3E;SCB isopod review&#x3C;/i&#x3E;
 at City of San Diego Environmental Monitoring Lab.</title>
<link>http://www.scamit.org/index.html#0b47b3996b6cce03b5d6b615322c3be6</link>
<description>Dr. Tim Stebbins will lead a review of the isopod fauna reported from the Southern California Bight. He will present images and discuss aspects of isopod taxonomy and ecology. This will be the first of several review meetings on isopods planned by Tim. </description>
</item>
</rdf:RDF>