<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<rdf:RDF
 xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
 xmlns="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/"
 xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
 xmlns:taxo="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/taxonomy/"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:syn="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
 xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/"
>

<channel rdf:about="">
<title>SCAMIT News and Events</title>
<link></link>
<description>Southern California Association of Marine Invertebrate Taxonomists</description>
<items>
 <rdf:Seq>
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#mesl" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#ecoanalysts" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://www.scamit.org/index.html#Oct18" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://www.scamit.org/index.html#Nov15" />
  <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://www.scamit.org/index.html#Dec11" />
 </rdf:Seq>
</items>
</channel>
<item rdf:about="http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#mesl">
<title>&#x3C;a name=&#x22;mesl&#x22;&#x3E;Marine Ecological Surveys&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
&#x3C;b&#x3E;Senior Marine Macrobenthic Taxonomist: Annelida&#x3C;/b&#x3E;
</title>
<link>http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#mesl</link>
<description>&#x3C;i&#x3E;1 September 2010&#x3C;br /&#x3E; We have the following vacancy at Marine Ecological Surveys Ltd (MESL). Deadline for applications has already expired, but we would be happy to consider further applications until the 15th of September 2010.&#x3C;br /&#x3E; Vacancy: Senior Marine Macrobenthic Taxonomist&#x3C;br /&#x3E; The MESL laboratory specialises in analysis of benthic and epibenthic samples from a wide variety of environments ranging from estuarine to offshore. Primarily our work consists of monitoring for the aggregate industry and, more recently, the renewable energy sector. Our staff comprise of an experienced team of marine biologists who are self-motivated and work to tight deadlines.&#x3C;br /&#x3E; We are looking for a senior marine macrobenthic taxonomist whose primary role will be to undertake analysis of benthic samples and identification of all taxonomic groups, together with training of junior staff in benthic taxonomy. You will be educated to at least degree level in marine biology or a related discipline and also have at least two years experience in marine invertebrate analysis and taxonomic identification. While you will be mostly lab-based, you will also be required to participate in fieldwork.&#x3C;br /&#x3E; MESL participates in the NMBAQC scheme, and in conjunction with this, we run our own internal training scheme to develop the taxonomic skills of our laboratory staff. We also encourage continued professional development for all our staff.&#x3C;br /&#x3E; Please email your CV to &#x3C;a href=&#x22;mailto:lab@seasurvey.co.uk&#x22;&#x3E;lab@seasurvey.co.uk&#x3C;/a&#x3E;&#x3C;br /&#x3E; Sara Marzialetti&#x3C;br /&#x3E; Senior Marine Ecologist&#x3C;br /&#x3E; Marine Ecological Surveys Limited&#x3C;br /&#x3E; 3 Palace Yard Mews&#x3C;br /&#x3E; Bath&#x3C;br /&#x3E; BA1 2NH&#x3C;br /&#x3E; England&#x3C;br /&#x3E; Tel: 01225 442211&#x3C;br /&#x3E; Fax: 01225 444411&#x3C;/i&#x3E;
</description>
</item>
<item rdf:about="http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#ecoanalysts">
<title>&#x3C;a name=&#x22;ecoanalysts&#x22;&#x3E;EcoAnalysts&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
&#x3C;b&#x3E;Multiple marine taxonomists&#x3C;/b&#x3E;
</title>
<link>http://www.scamit.org/jobs.html#ecoanalysts</link>
<description>&#x3C;i&#x3E;22 June 2010&#x3C;/i&#x3E;
&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 EcoAnalysts, Inc. has been awarded a contract by the US EPA to collect and analyze samples from the nation&#x27;s coasts in an effort to monitor and evaluate the ecological and environmental conditions in US waters. Please visit our Employment Opportunities page on our website at &#x3C;a href=&#x22;http://www.ecoanalysts.com&#x22;&#x3E;www.ecoanalysts.com&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
.&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
&#x3C;i&#x3E;Eric Torok&#x3C;/i&#x3E;
&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 Human Resources Coordinator&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 1420 S. Blaine St., Suite 14&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 Moscow, ID 83843&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
 etorok@ecoanalysts.com</description>
</item>
<item rdf:about="http://www.scamit.org/index.html#Oct18">
<title>&#x3C;a name=&#x22;Oct18&#x22;&#x3E;&#x3C;b&#x3E;Monday 18 October 2010 9:30 AM&#x3C;/b&#x3E;&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
&#x3C;i&#x3E;Bight&#x26;nbsp;&#x26;rsquo;08 synoptic data review meeting&#x3C;/i&#x3E;
 at SCCWRP Medium Conference Room.</title>
<link>http://www.scamit.org/index.html#Oct18</link>
<description>The compiled Bight&#xA0;&#x2019;08 species list from all stations will be reviewed for taxonomic consistency. The resulting final species list will be used in Bight&#xA0;&#x2019;08 infaunal data analyses. All Bight&#xA0;&#x2019;08 taxonomists are encouraged to attend this important meeting in case specific questions on taxonomic consistency arise.</description>
</item>
<item rdf:about="http://www.scamit.org/index.html#Nov15">
<title>&#x3C;a name=&#x22;Nov15&#x22;&#x3E;&#x3C;b&#x3E;Monday 15 November 2010 9:30 AM&#x3C;/b&#x3E;&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
&#x3C;i&#x3E;Mollusk literature review and Taxonomic Database testbed demo&#x3C;/i&#x3E;
 at OCSD meeting room.</title>
<link>http://www.scamit.org/index.html#Nov15</link>
<description>Mollusk literature review, followed by a demo of the testing version of the new Taxonomic Database. Non-mollusk taxonomists who are likely to be extensive users of the Taxonomic Database can attend the demo to see its features and provide feedback for further development.</description>
</item>
<item rdf:about="http://www.scamit.org/index.html#Dec11">
<title>&#x3C;a name=&#x22;Dec11&#x22;&#x3E;&#x3C;b&#x3E;Saturday 11 December 2010 5:30&#x26;ndash;9:00&#x26;nbsp;PM&#x3C;/b&#x3E;&#x3C;/a&#x3E;
&#x3C;br /&#x3E;
&#x3C;i&#x3E;SCAMIT Christmas Party&#x3C;/i&#x3E;
 at Cabrillo Marine Aquarium.</title>
<link>http://www.scamit.org/index.html#Dec11</link>
<description>All SCAMIT members and their families are invited to attend. In addition, the officers decided it would be neighborly to invite members and their families of our two sister groups to join us. Invitations will be extended to the members of the Southwestern Association of Freshwater Invertebrate Taxonomists (SAFIT) and the Southern California Association of Ichthyological Taxonomists and Ecologists (SCAITE). It should make for a lively event. More details later.</description>
</item>
</rdf:RDF>